Now that we've seen the fundamentals of
Langgraf, I want to review the agent itself
and how we're going to approach building it
over the course of this class.
了解了Langgraf的基础知识后，我想回顾一下智能体本身，以及我们将在本课程中如何构建它。
We're going to build an ambient agent that
can run your email. It's going to have four
main components.
我们将构建一个可以处理电子邮件的环境智能体，它将有四个主要组件。
The first is the agent itself, which we're
going to build first. You can see that in
blue.
第一个是智能体本身，我们将首先构建它。你可以在图中看到蓝色部分。
The second is actually testing it, which you
see in orange.
第二个是实际测试它，你可以在图中看到橙色部分。
We're going to show how to do that using
Langsmith.
我们将展示如何使用Langsmith来完成。
The third is adding human loop, and the
fourth is adding memory to learn preferences
over time.
第三个是添加人工循环，第四个是添加记忆，以便随着时间的推移学习偏好。
Now for building the agent itself, we're
going to use Langgraf as we've introduced,
现在，为了构建智能体本身，我们将使用我们介绍过的Langgraf，
and we're going to showcase how you can
combine an agent and specific workflow
components, notably a router, together into a
functioning system.
我们将展示如何将智能体和特定的工作流组件，特别是路由器，组合成一个功能系统。
While building this, we're going to be making
use of Langgraf Studio, as you saw previously
as well.
在构建过程中，我们将利用Langgraf Studio，正如你之前也看到的。
Now with this agent built, would you actually
turn it on? And many people would probably
say no. That's where testing comes in.
现在，如果这个智能体构建好了，你会真的打开它吗？很多人可能会说不。这就是测试的用武之地。
This is a survey we put out last year, asking
around 400 professionals, the major
challenges associated with building and
productionizing agents.
这是我们去年发布的一项调查，
Many mentioned performance, quality, cost,
safety, and latency.
询问了大约400名专业人士，关于构建和生产代理的主要挑战。
For these reasons, testing to benchmark the
performance of our agent is going to be very
important.
许多人提到了性能、质量、成本、安全性和延迟。
We'll show you to build datasets in
Langsmith, we'll show how to build tests in
Langsmith,
因此，测试以衡量我们代理的性能将非常重要。
and we'll show we can use this to actually
benchmark the performance of our agent.
我们将向您展示如何在Langsmith中构建数据集，如何在Langsmith中构建测试，
For an agent like this is oversight over our
email, the cost of error is very high.
并展示如何利用这些来实际衡量我们代理的性能。
So we're going to show how to incorporate
human loop with our agent.
对于像这样监督我们电子邮件的代理，出错的成本非常高。
We'll add human loop to get particular
sensitive actions, like certain tool calls.
所以我们将展示如何将人工干预与我们的代理结合起来。
We'll show agent inbox as a lightweight UX
for this.
我们将添加人工干预，以处理特定的敏感操作，例如某些工具调用。
Our agent will simply send all notifications
to inbox, or we can review, approve, or edit
specific tool calls, like sending the email
itself.
我们将展示Agent Inbox作为一种轻量级的用户体验。
Based upon the feedback we give the agent in
inbox, we're going to then update the agent's
memory.
根据我们在收件箱中给代理的反馈，我们将更新代理的记忆。
So it'll learn our preferences over time.
这样它就会随着时间推移了解我们的偏好。
So here's a map of the various lessons.
这是各种课程的地图。
We're going to start with building the email
system.
我们将从构建电子邮件系统开始。
We're then going to evaluate it using
Langsmith.
然后我们将使用Langsmith对其进行评估。
We'll then add human loop and show how to use
agent inbox, and finally wild memory and
deploy it.
接着我们将添加人工循环并展示如何使用代理收件箱，最后是野外记忆并部署它。
So now let's walk through the code of
actually building our agent.
现在让我们来看看实际构建代理的代码。
And to motivate it, I'm going to show you the
agent working in studio.
为了激发大家的兴趣，我将向大家展示代理在工作室中的工作情况。
This is what we're going to build.
这就是我们要构建的。
I can pass in an email, run, we'll triage the
email accordingly.
我可以传入一封电子邮件，运行，它会相应地分类电子邮件。
If triage determines that we should respond,
our response agent will use its tools to
respond appropriately.
如果分诊系统认为我们应该回应，我们的响应代理将使用其工具做出适当回应。
We can follow, in this particular case, the
input.
在这个特定案例中，我们可以遵循输入。
The triage router decides to respond to the
email.
分诊路由器决定回复这封邮件。
It passes the email in messages to our agent.
它将邮件作为消息传递给我们的代理。
Our agent then decides to make a tool call to
write email.
我们的代理随后决定调用工具来撰写邮件。
The tool call is executed.
工具调用被执行。
And then we finish.
然后我们完成。
So let's dive into the code now.
现在我们深入代码。
And we're in this blue block right here.
我们在这个蓝色方块里。
So that's what we're going to build out
first.
所以这是我们首先要构建的。
You've already seen how to define tools in
Langchain.
你已经了解了如何在 Langchain 中定义工具。
We're going to go ahead and define a few
tools that are relevant for an email system,
我们将定义一些与邮件系统相关的工具，
write email, schedule meeting, check calendar
availability, and done.
包括：写邮件、安排会议、查看日历空闲时间，以及完成。
Now, of course, these are just mock tools.
当然，这些只是模拟工具。
We're not actually hitting a real email API
for the purpose of this notebook and building
out our assistant.
为了本教程和构建助手，我们并没有真正调用邮件 API。
But the repo does have the option to connect
it into as an example Gmail, if you want to.
但如果你愿意，这个仓库确实提供了连接 Gmail 等示例的选项。
Now let's talk about the philosophy of
building our assistant.
现在，我们来谈谈构建助手的理念。
Remember, we talked about workflows in agents
previously.
记得我们之前讨论过代理中的工作流。
If we think about the control flow of our
application for every incoming email,
如果我们考虑应用程序的控制流，对于每一封收到的邮件，
we want to make some decision about it.
我们都希望对其做出一些决策。
Do we respond, just notify the user or ignore
it?
我们是回复、通知用户还是忽略？
Because this step we always want to do first,
we hard code this router as the first step in
our overall assistant.
因为我们总是想先执行这一步，所以我们将这个路由器硬编码为我们整个助手的第一个步骤。
And if the router decides to respond, we then
send to an agent.
如果路由器决定回复，我们就会发送给代理。
Now, why do you use an agent here?
那么，你为什么在这里使用代理呢？
Well, for the email response task, it's a
little bit more open ended.
嗯，对于电子邮件回复任务，它有点开放。
The tools you want to call depend a bit on
the content of the email itself.
你想调用的工具取决于电子邮件本身的内容。
As an example, sometimes you might respond
directly.
例如，有时你可能会直接回复。
Other times you might schedule a meeting.
其他时候你可能会安排会议。
Sometimes you might do both.
有时你可能会两者都做。
And so the email response process is a bit
more open ended.
因此，电子邮件回复过程有点开放。
And in that case, we use an agent.
这种情况下，我们会用到代理。
Now the nice thing is, we'll show how easy it
is to compose these two things in LandGraph.
接下来，我们会展示在LangGraph中组合这两者有多简单。
So let's build our router first.
我们先来构建路由器。
The router handles the triage decision.
路由器负责处理分类决策。
We'll define our state.
我们来定义一下状态。
We introduced this previously.
我们之前介绍过。
We'll just use messages state, which is that
prebuilt state object in LandGraph.
我们就用“messages”状态，它是LangGraph中预构建的状态对象。
And we'll add two new keys, email input and
classification decision.
我们会添加两个新键：“email input”和“classification
decision”。
So our state object in total has three keys,
messages, email input and classification
decision.
所以我们的状态对象总共有三个键：“messages”、“email
input”和“classification decision”。
Now we're going to define the triage node.
现在我们来定义分类节点。
I'm going to show a very simple but generally
nice trick for doing things like routing
using language models.
我会展示一个非常简单但通用的技巧，
Many language models support structured
outputs.
用于使用语言模型进行路由等操作。
In fact, that's what's happening when we
perform tool calling.
许多语言模型都支持结构化输出。
But because this is so common,
事实上，这就是我们进行工具调用时发生的事情。
our init chat model interface has a
particular method with structured output
where you can pass in a schema.
但因为这很常见，我们的初始聊天模型接口有一个特定的方法，
The output will be coerced to adhere to that
schema.
带有结构化输出，你可以在其中传入一个模式。
Here's an example where we pass the pedantic
model with two fields, reasoning and
classification.
输出将被强制符合该模式。
We provide descriptions of each field.
这是一个例子，我们传入了一个带有两个字段的严谨模型，
And when we bind this schema to our model,
分别是推理和分类。我们提供了每个字段的描述。
the model is aware of those descriptions and
uses them to help coerce its output to meet
this particular schema.
当我们将此模式绑定到我们的模型时，模型会意识到这些描述，
So what we're doing here is we're telling the
model to make a classification decision,
我们要让模型做出分类决定，
select from these three options, ignore,
respond or notify and give your reasoning.
从这三个选项中选择：忽略、回复或通知，并给出理由。
Now as we saw previously, we can pass in the
state.
之前我们看到，我们可以传入状态。
This state's going to contain an email input.
这个状态会包含一个电子邮件输入。
We'll just use some simple utils to parse it
and format some prompts that we have defined
in our repo,
我们会用一些简单的工具来解析它，并格式化我们在仓库中定义的提示，
triaging the incoming email.
用于分类传入的邮件。
We then invoke our router with a list of
messages that contains our prompts.
然后我们用包含提示的消息列表调用路由器。
And this output is going to be a structured
object that adheres the schema that we
passed.
输出会是一个结构化的对象，符合我们传入的模式。
So we can extract the classification decision
from that object.
我们可以从该对象中提取分类决定。
If the classification is respond, we're going
to go to the response agent.
如果分类是“回复”，我们就会转到回复代理。
And we're going to update our messages state
with the email so that the response agent
knows what to respond to.
我们将用邮件更新消息状态，
Now if the decision is to ignore or just
notify the user, we go to end and nothing
happens.
这样响应代理就知道该回复什么了。
In all cases, we update state with the
classification decision.
如果决定忽略或只通知用户，我们会结束，什么都不会发生。
Now you'll see something interesting here.
在所有情况下，我们都会用分类决策更新状态。
We return with this command object.
现在你会看到一些有趣的东西。
So what's happening here?
我们返回这个命令对象。
Before we talked about returning just with,
for example, a dict to update our state,
那么这里发生了什么？
command allows us to both update the state as
we see here with this update,
之前我们说过只返回一个字典来更新状态，
but also decide where to go next in our
graph.
命令允许我们像这里一样更新状态，
So it's a way of combining state updates and
control flow in a single step.
还可以决定下一步在图中去哪里。
So in this case, it just saves us a little
bit of time because we don't have to specify
all those edges from this particular node to
end or response agent.
这样能省点时间，因为我们不用指定从这个节点
Now here's where we'll build our agent.
到末端或响应代理的所有边。
Now we already have some good intuition for
building agents from before,
现在我们要构建代理了。
but in this case, I'm going to try to build
an agent with each node individually.
之前我们已经对构建代理有了很好的直觉，
So you can kind of see what's under the hood
of our create react agent abstraction.
但这次，我将尝试逐个节点地构建代理。
So first we just pull in our agent prompt.
这样你就能看到我们创建的反应代理抽象的内部原理了。
And this will just indicate the tools that
the agent has available to it and our agent
system prompt.
首先，我们引入代理提示。
And this is where we just very simply define
our instructions.
这将指示代理可用的工具和代理系统提示。
Now we'll define the node that makes our LM
call.
在这里，我们非常简单地定义了指令。
In this case, we define the tools as a list.
现在我们将定义进行语言模型调用的节点。
We bind them to our model.
我们将它们绑定到模型。
We format our prompt,
我们设置提示格式，
which includes tool descriptions as well as
any background preferences.
其中包括工具描述和任何背景偏好。
Updating our messages state with the LM
output.
用语言模型输出更新消息状态。
Now we define a node called tool handler,
现在我们定义一个名为“工具处理程序”的节点，
which will be responsible for just executing
the tool.
它将负责执行工具。
Remember, we saw all these principles
previously, so this is really nothing new.
请记住，我们之前已经了解了所有这些原则，所以这真的没什么新意。
We'll go ahead and get all the tool calls
from the prior message.
我们将从之前的消息中获取所有工具调用。
We'll invoke it and we'll update our state
with a tool message indicating the tool has
been called.
我们将调用它，并用一条工具消息更新我们的状态，表明工具已被调用。
Now here we'll add some simple conditional
routing,
现在我们在这里添加一些简单的条件路由，
which basically says continue calling tools
until the done tool is called.
基本上就是说，继续调用工具，直到调用了“完成”工具。
Remember before we use the termination
condition as no tool call has been executed.
记住，之前我们使用“没有工具调用被执行”作为终止条件。
In this case, a specific tool done is our
termination condition.
在这种情况下，一个特定的“完成”工具是我们的终止条件。
This is just another way to set up agents
with an alternative termination condition.
这只是设置代理的另一种方式，使用替代的终止条件。
Now we can lay out our agent graph.
现在我们可以布置我们的代理图。
This is very simple.
这非常简单。
We add our LM node.
我们添加我们的LM节点。
We add our tool handler node.
我们添加我们的工具处理程序节点。
We add our conditional edge to decide whether
or not to continue based upon the tool
called.
我们添加我们的条件边，根据调用的工具决定是否继续。
And we can see what's going to happen is the
LM will run,
我们可以看到将要发生的是LM将运行，
it will call a tool because we enforce tool
calling,
它会调用一个工具，因为我们强制它调用工具，
and it will continue calling tools until it
calls the done tool, at which point it'll
exit.
它会持续调用工具，直到调用“完成”工具，然后退出。
Now a very nice thing about Langrath is you
can easily compose different things.
LangGraph 的一个优点是，你可以轻松组合不同的东西。
Remember we previously defined our triage
router.
记得我们之前定义了分类路由器。
We can add the triage router as a node to
this larger workflow
我们可以将分类路由器作为一个节点添加到这个更大的工作流中，
and add our response agent, which we defined
here, as a node.
并将我们在这里定义的响应代理作为一个节点添加。
This effectively means that the agent is a
subgraph of our overall workflow.
这实际上意味着代理是我们整个工作流的一个子图。
We'll add a start edge to initiate the triage
router and we'll compile our graph.
我们将添加一个起始边来启动分类路由器，然后编译我们的图。
So now you can see we go to the triage
router.
所以现在你可以看到我们进入了分类路由器。
Depending on the decision made by the triage
router,
根据分类路由器做出的决定，
we may go to the response agent, which will
handle the email response, and then we'll
end.
我们会把邮件交给响应代理，由它来处理邮件回复，然后就结束了。
Now let's test running it.
现在我们来测试运行一下。
In this case you can see the classification
decision is just notify and nothing else
happens.
在这个例子中，你可以看到分类决定只是通知，没有其他操作。
Now let's try with an email for which we're
expected to respond.
现在我们来试试一封需要回复的邮件。
The decision is to respond.
决定是回复。
Now to see something interesting.
现在来看看一些有趣的东西。
The initial message is the email.
初始消息就是这封邮件。
With this appended respond to this email.
后面附加了“回复这封邮件”。
Where did that happen?
这是怎么发生的？
Remember that was actually done up in the
triage router.
记住，这实际上是在分流路由器中完成的。
If the triage router makes a decision to
respond, all we need to do is update the
state of our graph
如果分诊路由器决定响应，我们只需更新图的状态
with an initial message saying respond to
this email.
并附上初始消息，写上“回复这封邮件”。
The agent subgraph used that messages key.
代理子图使用了消息键。
So it received then that message from the
router and could in turn respond to it.
所以它从路由器那里收到了消息，并能反过来响应它。
That's the beauty of using this state object.
这就是使用状态对象的好处。
It's passed between the nodes of your graph
and our router can communicate with our agent
very simply through state.
它在图的节点之间传递，我们的路由器可以通过状态非常简单地与代理通信。
And we can see a call email tool is done and
we end.
我们可以看到“调用邮件工具”已完成，然后结束。
Now just to bookend this.
现在，为了首尾呼应。
Remember we ran land graph dev.
记住我们运行了“land graph dev”。
To start a local deployment.
来启动本地部署。
Which allows us to use land graph studio to
interact with our agent.
这样我们就能用LangGraph Studio
So here's what you'll see when you open
studio.
和我们的智能体交互了。
Again, you can just select various agents
from your drop down list.
这就是你打开Studio后看到的界面。
Go to email system.
你可以从下拉列表中选择不同的智能体。
Here is the graph we actually just built in
the notebook.
进入邮件系统。
Now what you can do is open this up and you
can see our agent subgraph inside here.
这就是我们刚才在Notebook中构建的图。
Pass an email.
现在你可以打开它，看到里面的智能体子图。
The router classifies it.
传入一封邮件。
The response agent handles it and we finish.
路由器对其进行分类。
So this reproduces what we saw in the
notebook, but in a nice visual environment.
响应智能体处理它，然后结束。
And you can inspect each step if you'd like.
你可以查看每一步。
And the state updates made.
以及状态更新。
You can see we finally go to done.
最终我们完成了。
And as mentioned before, you can click open
run Lang Smith.
如前所述，你可以点击“打开运行LangSmith”。
And we can now view the trace.
现在我们可以查看跟踪。
We can see here's our triage router.
我们可以看到这是我们的分类路由器。
This is the triage decision.
这是分类决策。
You can look at all the prompts used.
你可以查看所有使用的提示。
And then you can look at the agent itself.
然后你可以查看代理本身。
The agent made a tool call to write email.
代理调用了工具来编写邮件。
And then it called the done tool to end.
然后它调用“完成”工具来结束。
So now you've seen how to build an agent from
scratch.
现在你已经学会了如何从头开始构建一个智能体。
How to connect it in a workflow to a router.
如何在工作流中将其连接到路由器。
How to run it.
如何运行它。
And how to visualize it in studio.
以及如何在Studio中可视化它。
So now we can build from here to evaluate it.
现在我们可以以此为基础进行评估。
Add human loop and then finally add memory.
添加人工循环，最后添加记忆。